{
  "difficultquestions": [
    {
      "question": "What ____ their _____? Alexander and Philip.",
      "answer1": "are / name",
      "answer2": "is / name",
      "answer3": "is / names",
      "answer4": "are / names",
      "correct": "are / names"
    },
    {
      "question": "I ______ 22 years old, but Andrew ______ 2.",
      "answer1": "am / am",
      "answer2": "are / am",
      "answer3": "am / is",
      "answer4": "are / are",
      "correct": "am / is"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mark______ 19, but Brian and Denise ______ 26 and 28",
      "answer1": "is / are",
      "answer2": "are / is",
      "answer3": "are / are",
      "answer4": "am / are",
      "correct": "is / are"
    },
    {
      "question": " “What ______ this?”\n“It’s ______ umbrella.”",
      "answer1": "are / a",
      "answer2": "is / a",
      "answer3": "is / an",
      "answer4": "its / an",
      "correct": "is / an"
    },
    {
      "question": "How old is your aunt?\n ______ is 29.”",
      "answer1": "She",
      "answer2": "He",
      "answer3": "She's",
      "answer4": "He's",
      "correct": "She's"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where ______ she from?\nShe ______ from Japan.",
      "answer1": "are / is",
      "answer2": "is / is",
      "answer3": "is / am",
      "answer4": "are / are",
      "correct": "is / is"
    },
    {
      "question": "This ______ my friend. ______ name’s Richard.",
      "answer1": "are / His",
      "answer2": "s / My",
      "answer3": "is / His",
      "answer4": "his / His",
      "correct": "is / His"
    },
    {
      "question": "They ______ Lisa and Max. They ______ from the USA.",
      "answer1": " is / is",
      "answer2": "are / is",
      "answer3": "are / are",
      "answer4": "is / is",
      "correct": "are / are"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is ______ name? My name's Carlos.",
      "answer1": "feel",
      "answer2": "each",
      "answer3": "yohit",
      "answer4": "my",
      "correct": "your"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is my sister. ______ name is Laura.",
      "answer1": "Feel",
      "answer2": "My",
      "answer3": "Any",
      "answer4": "Dogs",
      "correct": "Any"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have ______ brother. ______ name is David",
      "answer1": "an / Sense",
      "answer2": "a / Her",
      "answer3": "a / His",
      "answer4": "* / Sense",
      "correct": "a / His"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hello! My ___ ___ Maria. I ___ ___ Mexico.",
      "answer1": "name is / from am",
      "answer2": "is name / from am",
      "answer3": "name is / am from",
      "answer4": "name am / is from",
      "correct": "name is / am from"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is Catherine ______ sister?",
      "answer1": "he",
      "answer2": "you",
      "answer3": "your",
      "answer4": "yours",
      "correct": "your"
    },
    {
      "question": "We ______ students.",
      "answer1": "are a",
      "answer2": "is",
      "answer3": "are",
      "answer4": "am",
      "correct": "are"
    },
    {
      "question": "I ______ student.",
      "answer1": "is / an",
      "answer2": "am / *",
      "answer3": "am / a",
      "answer4": "am / the",
      "correct": "am / a"
    },
    {
      "question": "She ______ Italy",
      "answer1": "are from",
      "answer2": "is at",
      "answer3": "is from",
      "answer4": "am from",
      "correct": "is from"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is ______ teacher",
      "answer1": "a",
      "answer2": "an",
      "answer3": "*",
      "answer4": "the",
      "correct": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "I live ______ a house ______ Los Angeles",
      "answer1": " * / in",
      "answer2": "in / in",
      "answer3": "in / *",
      "answer4": "at / in",
      "correct": "in / in"
    },
    {
      "question": "“______ is your phone number?”\n“It’s 2229\"",
      "answer1": "Where",
      "answer2": "How",
      "answer3": "What",
      "answer4": "Who",
      "correct": "What"
    },
    {
      "question": "______ are you?\nI'm Alex.",
      "answer1": "Which",
      "answer2": "How",
      "answer3": "What",
      "answer4": "Who",
      "correct": "Who"
    },
    {
      "question": "What's this ______ English?",
      "answer1": "*",
      "answer2": "in",
      "answer3": "at",
      "answer4": "on",
      "correct": "in"
    },
    {
      "question": "Champaigne is ______ French drink.",
      "answer1": "a",
      "answer2": "the",
      "answer3": "an",
      "answer4": "*",
      "correct": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Oxford is ______ English university.",
      "answer1": "a",
      "answer2": "an",
      "answer3": "the",
      "answer4": "*",
      "correct": "an"
    },
    {
      "question": "A Mercedes is ______ German car",
      "answer1": "a",
      "answer2": "an",
      "answer3": "the",
      "answer4": "*",
      "correct": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "English is ______ international language.",
      "answer1": "a",
      "answer2": "an",
      "answer3": "the",
      "answer4": "*",
      "correct": "an"
    },
    {
      "question": "Milan is ______ Italian city.",
      "answer1": "a",
      "answer2": "an",
      "answer3": "the",
      "answer4": "*",
      "correct": "an"
    },
    {
      "question": "A JVC is ______ Japanese camera",
      "answer1": "a",
      "answer2": "an",
      "answer3": "the",
      "answer4": "*",
      "correct": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have two ______ .",
      "answer1": "sister",
      "answer2": "sisters",
      "answer3": "a sister",
      "answer4": "sister's",
      "correct": "sisters"
    },
    {
      "question": "It’s ______ Spanish orange.",
      "answer1": "a",
      "answer2": "an",
      "answer3": "the",
      "answer4": "*",
      "correct": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "It’s ______ green apple.",
      "answer1": "a",
      "answer2": "an",
      "answer3": "the",
      "answer4": "*",
      "correct": "a"
    }
  ]
}